Guide to the Lucy Monroe Calhoun Family Photographs and Papers, 1886-1993 and undated, bulk 1911-1933 RL.11103
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Developing out paper and gelatin silver photographs, 1900-1941 and undated; 1
  - Outside Beijing, 1900-1939; 3
    - Near the Summer Palace, belonged to Prince Chun, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-320)
      Near the Summer Palace, belonged to Prince Chun
    - Canal at Summer Palace, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-321)
      颐和园水渠
    - Grasses along canal--Summer Palace road, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-322)
      颐和园昆明湖边芦苇
      Grasses along canal--Summer Palace road
    - Summer Palace bridge detail, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-323)
      颐和园金水桥
      Summer Palace?
    - Eastern Palace Gate, detail, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-324)
      颐和园排云门铜狮
    - Eastern Palace Gate, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-325)
      F'si Yun Men T'ung Shih
    - 17-Arch Bridge, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-326)
      颐和园十七拱桥
      Bridge at Summer Palace
    - Bronze ox in marble pen, with 17-Arch Bridge in background, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-327)
      颐和园十七拱桥旁的铜牛
    - Bronze ox in marble pen, with 17-Arch Bridge in background, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-328)
      Bronze cow in marble pen. Shih Ch'i K'ung Ch'iao Ch'uan
    - Hou Da Miao (Xu Mi Ling Jing), Buddhist temples, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-329)
      颐和园后大庙（须弥灵境）全景
      Hoa Ta Miao Ch'uan Ching
    - Hall of Dispelling Clouds, from main boat landing, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-330)
      颐和园万寿山排云殿及后面的佛香阁
      Looking up from main boat landing. P'ai Yun Tien
    - Stele of Longevity Hill, Wanshou Hill, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-331)
      颐和园万寿山石碑
      W'an Shou Shan Shih Pei
    - Bronze Pavilion, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-332)
      颐和园万寿山铜亭（宝云阁）
      T'ung T'ing Tzo
    - Huazhongyou on Longevity Hill, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-333)
      颐和园万寿山画中游
      Hua Chung You
    - Building at Summer Palace, Tower of Buddhist Incense in background, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-334)
      颐和园万寿山佛香阁
    - Longevity Hill, from Kunming Lake, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-335)
      颐和园万寿山西面全景
      Hai Ch'uan Ching
    - Shuimuziqin Hall, Tower of Buddhist Incense, from lake, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-336)
      颐和园昆明湖北岸水木自亲殿，殿前灯架和后面的佛香阁
      Shui Mu Tzu Ch'ien Tai Ch'uan
    - Zhichun Pavillion, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-337)
      颐和园昆明湖东岸知春亭
      Chih Ch'un T'ing Tai Chuan
    - Renshou Gate, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-338)
      颐和园东宫仁寿门
      Jen Shou Men
    - Xing Bridge, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-339)
      颐和园荇桥
      Hsing Ch'iao
    - Hall of Joy and Longevity, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-340)
      颐和园乐寿堂
      Le Shou T'ang
    - Hall of Benevolence and Longevity, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-341)
      颐和园仁寿殿
      Jen Shou Tien
    - Garden of Harmonious Pleasures, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-342)
      颐和园谐趣园
      Hsieh Chu Yuan
    - One of the barges and old steam boat, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-343)
      颐和园大船坞
      One of the barges and old steam boat. Ta Ch'uan Wu
    - Stone boat, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-344)
      颐和园石舫
      Marble boat where we had tea
    - Yunhuiyuyu Pai Lou, 1920s; 5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-345)
      颐和园云辉玉宇牌楼
      Boat landing. Pai Lou
    - Long Corridor, 1920s; 3.25 x 5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-346)
      颐和园长廊
      Long open gallery about 2 blocks long with lake on one side. Ch'ang Lang
    - Jietai Temple, a group of monks entering a temple, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-347.1)
      北京西山戒台寺，僧人们走入佛堂
      Chieh Tai Ssu
    - Jietai Temple, a group of monks entering a temple, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-347.2)
      The Western Hills, Peking. Chieh Tai Ssu, Lucy Calhoun. Calhoun
      Version of RL11103-347.1.
    - Jietai Temple, man leaning against a terrace wall, with a child nearby, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-348.1)
      北京西山戒台寺，僧人倚栏杆
    - Jietai Temple, man leaning against a terrace wall, with a child nearby, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-348.2)
      Version of RL11103-348.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Jietai Temple, Large tree in courtyard, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-349.1)
      北京西山戒台寺，院中古树
    - Jietai Temple, Large tree in courtyard, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-349.2)
      Version of RL11103-349.1.
    - Jietai Temple, courtyard with large pinetree, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-350.1)
      北京西山戒台寺，院中高大松树
    - Jietai Temple, courtyard with large pinetree, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-350.2)
      Version of RL11103-350.1.
    - Jietai Temple, pinetree and building, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-351.1)
      北京西山戒台寺，院中松树和佛堂
    - Jietai Temple, pinetree and building, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-351.2)
      Version of RL11103-351.1.
    - Jietai Temple courtyard, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-352.1)
      北京西山戒台寺院内
    - Jietai Temple courtyard, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-352.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-352.1.
    - Jietai Temple terrace, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-353)
      北京西山戒台寺院落和石栏
      Terrace--Chieh Tai Ssu
    - Jietai Temple, two pagodas, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-354)
      北京西山戒台寺，两座石塔
    - Multiple pagodas, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-355.1)
      北京西山潭柘寺塔林
      T'an Che Szo
    - Multiple pagodas, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-355.2)
      The Western Hills-- Peking. Tan Che Ssu. Lucy Calhoun. Calhoun.
      Version of RL11103-355.1.
    - Multiple pagodas, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-355.3)
      Chieh Tai Sse
    - Jietai Temple, detail of wall, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-356)
      北京西山戒台寺石栏
    - Western visitors gathered near stone lion at Tan Chi Sse (Tanzhe Temple), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-357.1)
      北京西山潭柘寺山门石狮子旁的外国游客
    - Western visitors gathered near stone lion at Tan Chi Sse (Tanzhe Temple), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-357.2)
      Tan Chi Sse
      Version of RL11103-357.1.
    - Jietai Temple, dining on the terrace, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-358)
      北京西山戒台寺院中用餐
    - Beyond Chieh Tai Ssu (Jietai Temple), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-359)
      戒台寺远眺西山
      Photo by Miss May. Beyond Chieh Tai Ssu.
    - From Chieh Tai Ssu (Jietai Temple), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-360)
      Photo by Miss May. From Chieh Tai Ssu.
    - Hei Lung Tang (Heilongtan) wisteria, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-361.1)
      北京西山黑龙潭的寺庙和树木
      Hei Lung Tang wisteria
    - Hei Lung Tang (Heilongtan) wisteria, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 8, Print RL11103-P-361.2)
      The Western Hills, Peking. Hei Lung Tang. Lucy Calhoun. Calhoun
    - Hsiang Chieh Ssu (Xiangjie Temple), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 9, Print RL11103-P-362)
      北京西山八大处香界寺
      The Western Hills, Peking. Hsiang Chieh Ssu. Lucy Calhoun. Calhoun
    - Hsiang Chieh Ssu (Xiangjie Temple) courtyard, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 9, Print RL11103-P-363.1)
      北京西山八大处香界寺院中
      Hsiang Chieh Ssu at Pa Ta Chu
    - Hsiang Chieh Ssu (Xiangjie Temple) courtyard, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 9, Print RL11103-P-363.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-363.1.
    - Hsiang Chieh Ssu (Xiangjie Temple) garden, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 9, Print RL11103-P-364)
      北京西山八大处香界寺院子
    - Lung Wang Tang (Longwang Tang) doorway, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-365)
      北京西山八大处龙王堂大门
      The Western Hills, Peking. Lung Wang Tang. Lucy Calhoun. Calhoun
    - Lung Wang Tang (Longwang Tang) stairway, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-366)
      北京西山八大处龙王堂台阶
      The Western Hills, Peking. Lung Wang Tang. Lucy Calhoun.
    - Gates at Lung Wang Tang (Longwang Tang), 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-367.1)
      北京西山八大处龙王堂的院门
      Lung Wang Tang at Pa Ta Chu
    - Gates at Lung Wang Tang (Longwang Tang), 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-367.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-367.1.
    - Terrace at Lung Wang Tang (Longwang Tang), 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-368.1)
      北京西山八大处龙王堂院中香炉
    - Terrace at Lung Wang Tang (Longwang Tang), 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 10, Print RL11103-P-368.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-368.1.
    - Lingguang Temple's Pa-Li-Chuan pagoda, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-369)
      北京西山八大处灵光寺的佛牙舍利塔
      The Western Hills, Peking. Pa-Li-Chuan. Lucy Calhoun. Calhoun
    - Ta Pei Ssu (Dabei Temple) terraces., 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 12, Print RL11103-P-370)
      北京西山八大处大悲寺
      The Western Hills, Peking. Ta Pei Ssu. Lucy Calhoun. Calhoun
    - Ta Pei Ssu (Dabei Temple) courtyard, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 12, Print RL11103-P-371)
    - Abbot -- Tan Chi Sse (Tanzhe Temple), 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-372)
      北京西山潭柘寺住持
      Abbot -- Tan Chi Sse
    - Old abbot -- Tan Chi Sse (Tanzhe Temple), 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-373)
      Old abbot -- Tan Chi Sse
    - Tanzhe Temple, Qixuan Pavillion, Carl Patterson, ?, Polly Root Collier, Ratay, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-374)
      北京西山潭柘寺绮轩亭合影：卡尔·帕特森，波莉·鲁特·科利尔，瑞特
      Carl Patterson, ?, PRC, Ratay
    - Visit to Qixuan Pavilion, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-375)
      北京西山潭柘寺绮轩亭合影
    - Treasure House -- Tan Chi Sse (Tanzhe Temple), 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-376)
      北京西山潭柘寺楞严坛
      Treasure House -- Tan Chi Sse
    - Dragon Pool Pavilion -- Tan Chi Sse (Tanzhe Temple), 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-377)
      北京西山潭柘寺绮轩亭
      Dragon Pool Pavillion -- Tan Chi Sse
    - Pagodas and large tree, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-378)
      北京西山潭柘寺塔林和树木
      Tan Che Sse
    - Courtyard tree, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-379.1)
      北京西山潭柘寺院中古树
      T'an Che Szu
    - Courtyard tree, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-379.2)
      Version of RL11103-379.1.
    - Courtyard tree, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-379.3)
    - Stairway, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-380)
      北京西山潭柘寺院中石阶
      Tan Chi Ssu
    - Lady at top of stairway, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-381.1)
      北京西山潭柘寺院中石阶上站立的女士
    - Lady at top of stairway, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-381.2)
      Stairway, Tan Chi Sse
      Version of RL11103-381.1.
    - Terrace, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-382)
      北京西山潭柘寺
    - Sunlight in courtyard, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-383)
      北京西山潭柘寺，阳光照入院中
    - Table laid for tiffin, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-384)
      北京西山潭柘寺，院中摆好桌子
      Tan Chi See. Table Laid for Tiffin.
    - Court, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-385)
      北京西山潭柘寺院中
      Court. Tan Chi Sse
    - The pool, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-386.1)
      北京西山潭柘寺，水池
      Tan Chi Ssu. The pool.
    - The pool, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-386.2)
      The Western Hills-- Peking. Tan Che Ssu. Lucy Calhoun. Calhoun. Top. Top.
      Version of RL11103-386.1.
    - Ginko tree, 1000 years old, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-387.1)
      北京西山潭柘寺，千年银杏树
      Tan Chi Ssu. Ginko tree, 1000 years old
    - Ginko tree, 1000 years old, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-387.2)
      Version of RL11103-387.1.
    - Main hall (back), Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-388.1)
      北京西山潭柘寺，大雄宝殿
      Library. Tan Chi Sse
    - Main hall (back), Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-388.2)
      北京西山潭柘寺，大雄宝殿（背面）
      Version of RL11103-388.1.
    - Main hall, front, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-389.1)
      北京西山潭柘寺，大雄宝殿（正面）
    - Main hall, front, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-389.2)
    - Main courtyard at Tan Chi Sse (Tanzhe Temple), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-390.1)
      北京西山潭柘寺山门
    - Main courtyard at Tan Chi Sse (Tanzhe Temple), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-390.2)
      Version of RL11103-390.1.
    - Dancing goddess on altar, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-391.1)
      北京西山潭柘寺菩萨塑像
      Dancing Goddess. Tan Chi Sse
    - Dancing goddess on altar, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-391.2)
      Version of RL11103-391.1.
    - Altar, with hanging, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-392.1)
      北京西山潭柘寺佛塑像
    - Altar, with hanging, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-392.2)
      Version of RL11103-392.1.
    - Two statues on altar, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-393)
      北京西山潭柘寺观音塑像
    - Dancing goddess, detail, Tanzhe Temple., 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-394)
    - Robed statue on altar, Tanzhe Temple, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 13, Print RL11103-P-395)
    - Tien Tai Shan (Tiantai Mountain), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 14, Print RL11103-P-396)
      北京西山天台山上的寺庙
      The Western Hills--Peking. Tien Tai Shan
    - Wu Tai Shan pool., 1930s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 15, Print RL11103-P-397.1)
      五台山
    - Wu Tai Shan pool., 1930s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 15, Print RL11103-P-397.2)
      Wu Tai Chien
    - Pagoda at Wu Tai Shan, 1930s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 15, Print RL11103-P-398)
      五台山佛塔
      Trip to Wu Tai Shan
    - Altar at Wu Tai Shan, 1930s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 15, Print RL11103-P-399)
      五台山寺庙内佛像
    - Altar at Wu Tai Shan, detail, 1930s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 15, Print RL11103-P-400)
      五台山寺庙内观音像
      Wu Tai Shan
    - Angkor Wat, the causeway, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-401)
      吴哥窟，大道
      Ankhor 12 Ankhor Wat The Causeway
    - Angkor Wat rubble, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-402)
      吴哥窟残留建筑
    - Elephant wall, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-403)
      吴哥窟大象墙
    - Angkor Wat galleries, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-404)
      吴哥窟画廊
      Angkor
    - Angkor Wat library, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-405)
      吴哥窟藏书室
    - Angkor Wat gallery, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-406.1)
    - Angkor Wat gallery, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-406.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-406.1.
    - Corridor with bas relief, 1912; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-407)
      吴哥窟画廊的浅浮雕
    - tree in rubble, 1912; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-408.1)
      吴哥窟残留建筑和树林
    - tree in rubble, 1912; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-408.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-408.1.
    - tree in rubble, 1912; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-408.3)
      Copy of RL11103-P-408.2.
    - Wall of elephant carvings, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-409.1)
      吴哥窟墙上的大象浮雕
    - Wall of elephant carvings, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-409.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-409.1.
    - Bas relief around window, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-410.1)
      吴哥窟，窗户旁的浅浮雕
    - Bas relief around window, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-410.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-410.1.
    - Bas relief around window, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-410.3)
    - Bas relief in sunlight, 1912; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-411)
      吴哥窟，阳光照耀下的浅浮雕
    - Bas relief on outter wall, 1912; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-412)
      吴哥窟，外墙上的浅浮雕
    - Angkor Wat viewed from rear, 1912; 3.25 x 5.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 16, Print RL11103-P-413)
      吴哥窟后面
      Gratis
    - Shogun's Palace, Nijo Castle, 1931; 4 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-414)
      Title (Japanese)
      二条城
      Shogun's Palace, Nijo Castle, Sept. 2, where old [paintings?] are
    - Kiyomizu-dera temple, 1931; 4 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-415)
      清水寺
      Kiyo [midzu} Temple on Teapot Hill. Aug. 3. various temples given by [demons?] -- waterfall used in [winter] by penetents -- temple for sick children
    - Chion-in Temple, 1931; 4 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-416)
      知恩院
      Gate of Cho-in Temple. Aug 31. 1st temple-- pray for souls by beating drum continually
    - Kiyomizu-dera pagoda, 1931; 3 x 4 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-417)
      清水寺塔
    - Kyoto Torii, 1931; 3 x 4 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-418)
      京都鳥居
      Kyoto -- Torü. Made to commemorate Emperor's coronation. of concrete.
    - Higashi Honganji temple, 1931; 4 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-419)
      東本願寺
      [Hungashi] Honganji Sept. 2, has marvellous [sic.] flying angels in frieze of large temple--Buddha behind screen. In another temple, frieze of phoenix-standing Buddha. [easiest?] form of religion-- several [illegible] belong to this temple-- ropes of women's hair to raise great pillars of [illegible] 98 of them. take 2 men to span
    - [Hashidono bridge? (Taihei-kaku) in the Gardens of Heian Jingu Shrine, Kyoto], 1931; 4 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-420)
      平安神宮, 泰平閣 (橋殿)
      Bridge in Heiherian Temple. Aug. 31. where we watched gold fist & carp. [illegible] cherry trees -- azaleas -- [illegible] with children
    - Silver Pavilion Ginkakuji, 1931; 4 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-421)
      銀閣寺
      Silver Pavilion. Sept. 2
    - Palace, 1931; 4 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-422)
      京都御所
      Palace. Sept. 2. coronation hall -- waiting room for Lords -- modern [picture] -- shorter [illegible]
    - Higashi Honganji temple fountain, 1931; 4 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-423)
      東本願寺前の蓮花型噴水
      Fountain. [Hungashi] Honganji Temple
    - Deer in a Japanese temple, 1931; 3.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-424)
      鹿
      Deer in a Japanese temple
    - Street scene, 1931; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-425)
      当時の通りの風景
    - William J. Calhoun at Kyoto, 1910s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 17, Print RL11103-P-426)
      カルフーン ウィリアム J.
      Kyoto in April. Uncle Cal.
    - Gov. Forbes, 1912; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-427.1)
      美国驻菲律宾总督福布斯
      Gov. Forbes
    - Gov. Forbes, 1912; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-427.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-427.1.
    - Gov. Forbes & Willard [Straight] at Malacañang Palace, 1912; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-428)
      美国驻菲律宾总督福布斯和威廉·司戴德, 马拉坎南宫
      Gov. Forbes & Willard at Mala canyon
    - Left- Gov. Forbes, Middle- Willard Straight, [Right- unknown], 1912; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-429)
      左边-美国驻菲律宾总督福布斯，中间-威廉·司戴德,
      Left- Gov. Forbes, Middle- Willard Straight
    - Gov. Forbes and Igorots, 1912; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-430)
      美国驻菲律宾总督福布斯和伊戈罗特女孩们
      Gov. & Igerotes
    - Gov. Forbes and Igorots, including a young girl, 1912; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-431)
    - Gov's staff + Polly Root Collier 2nd from left, 1912; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-432.1)
      美国驻菲律宾总督府工作人员，左边第二个是波丽·鲁特
      Gov's staff + Polly 2nd from left
    - Gov's staff + Polly Root Collier 2nd from left, 1912; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-432.2)
      鲍迪彼得·伯德韦奇奇
      Version of RL11103-P-432.1.
    - Polly Root Collier and Dorothy Straight, middle, 1912; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-433)
      合影中间是波丽·鲁特和多萝西·司戴德
      Polly & Dorothy - middle
    - Peter Bowditch, 1912; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-434)
      彼得·鲍迪奇
      Peter Bowditch
    - Dorothy Whitney Straight, 1912; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-435)
      多萝西·惠特尼·司戴德
      Dorothy Whitney Straight
    - Dorothy Straight, 1912; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-436)
      多萝西·司戴德
      Dorothy Straight
    - Unidentified man with one sleeve rolled up, 1912; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-437)
      未知姓名的男子，衣袖卷起
    - unidentified house in Manila, 1912; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-438)
      马尼拉房屋
    - Cottage - on grounds of Gov. house in Manila- which we occupied, 1912; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-439)
      到访马尼拉时居住的房屋，总督房子附近
      Cottage - on grounds of Gov. house- which we occupied
    - Governor's house in Manila, 1912; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-440)
      马尼拉美国总督住的房子
      Governor's house
    - House on stilts in Manila, 1912; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-441)
      马尼拉干栏屋
    - Houses on stilts in Manila, 1912; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-442)
    - Filipino woman holding a child, 1912; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-443)
      抱婴儿的菲律宾妇女
    - Unidentified church, Old City, Manila, 1910s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-444)
      马尼拉老城的一座教堂
    - Fountain in park, Old City, Manila, 1910s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-445)
      马尼拉老城的一座建筑和喷泉
    - wall, Old City, Manila, 1910s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-446)
      马尼拉老城的一段围墙
    - Park-like area, Old City, Manila, 1910s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-447)
      马尼拉老城的一处风景优美的地方
    - Domed building, Old City, Manila, 1910s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-448)
      马尼拉老城的一座圆顶建筑
    - Fountain with statue, Old City, Manila, 1910s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-449)
      马尼拉老城的一处喷泉和中间的雕塑
    - Gate with four columns. Old City, Manila, 1910s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-450)
      马尼拉老城一个有四个柱子的大门
    - Gate with two columns. Old City, Manila, 1910s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 18, Print RL11103-P-451)
      马尼拉老城一个有两个柱子的大门
    - Temple of Quetzalcoatl stairs, 1930s; 3.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 19, Print RL11103-P-452)
      墨西哥羽蛇神庙的台阶